(audience cheers and applauds)
- Thanks.
Remember, in the end, nobody
wins unless everybody wins.
Come on!
One, two!
("Born to Run" by Bruce Springsteen)
♪ In the day we sweat
it out on the streets ♪
♪ Of a runaway American dream ♪
♪ At night we ride through
mansions of glory ♪
♪ In suicide machines ♪
♪ Sprung from cages out on Highway 9 ♪
♪ Chrome wheeled fuel injected ♪
♪ And steppin' out over the line ♪
♪ Oh baby this town rips
the bones from your back ♪
♪ It's a death trap it's a suicide rap ♪
♪ We gotta get out while we're young ♪
♪ 'Cause tramps like us
baby we were born to run ♪
♪ Wendy let me in I wanna be your friend ♪
♪ I want to guard your
dreams and visions ♪
♪ Just wrap your legs
'round these velvet rims ♪
♪ And strap your hands across my engines ♪
♪ Together we could break this trap ♪
♪ We'll run till we drop
baby we'll never go back ♪
♪ Oh will you walk with
me out on the wire ♪
♪ 'Cause baby I'm just a
scared and lonely rider ♪
♪ But I gotta know how it feels ♪
♪ I want to know if love is wild babe ♪
♪ I want to know if love is real ♪
♪ Oh can you show me ♪
♪ Beyond the palace hemi-powered drones ♪
♪ Scream down the boulevard ♪
♪ The girls comb their
hair in rearview mirrors ♪
♪ And the boys try to look so hard ♪
♪ The amusement park
rises bold and stark ♪
♪ Kids are huddled on
the beach in a mist ♪
♪ I wanna die with you Wendy
on the streets tonight ♪
♪ In an everlasting kiss ♪
♪ One two three ♪
♪ The highways jammed with broken heroes ♪
♪ On a last chance power drive ♪
♪ Everybody's out on the run tonight ♪
♪ But there's no place left to hide ♪
♪ Together Wendy we can
live with the sadness ♪
♪ I'll love you with all
the madness in my soul ♪
♪ Oh someday girl I don't know when ♪
♪ We're gonna get to that place ♪
♪ Where we really want to go
and we'll walk in the sun ♪
♪ But till then tramps like us ♪
♪ Baby we were born to run ♪
♪ Oh tramps like us ♪
♪ With me tramps like us ♪
♪ Baby we were born to run ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪